get-more.me 2013-07-20

# Platform and Services Privacy Policy

                                Platform and Services Privacy Policy
Last updated: June 25, 2013
Get-more.me ("Get-more.me" "we", "our" or "us") has created a technology platform (the
"Platform") and provides related services via the Platform (the "Service") that our customers, which
are typically advertisers and ad agencies use to optimize their delivery and management of online
advertising campaigns, including interest-based advertising. The Platform is designed to enable these
advertising purposes through the use of non- PII (as defined below) that may be collected by
customers using the Platform, or that customers may acquire from other sources.
We respect the privacy of Internet users in general ("users") and wish to set forth in this Privacy
Policy ("Policy") Get-more.me. Get-more.me’s practices in connection with the collection and use of
information. Please note that this Policy applies only to Get-more.me and does not state the use
practices or policies of our customers, of the websites on which ads are shown, or of other third
parties.
This Policy is in reference to the use of our Service.
This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Get-more.me does not own or control
or to people it does not employ or manage.
WHAT TYPES OF INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?
We do not collect or use any Personally Identifiable Information (or "PII") via the Platform and
Service. "PII" is information that by itself can be used to identify a specific individual and includes
such things as name, address, phone number, and email address. Get-more.me further prohibits its
customers from providing PII for use on the Platform.
We also do not collect sensitive consumer information, such as credit card numbers or financial
account numbers.
We collect only anonymous, non-Personally Identifiable Information; "non-PII" is information that
cannot by itself be used to identify an individual person and includes such things as browser type,
operating system, IP address, the web address of a web page visited, the time and date a web page
was visited, and the web address of the referring page. It may also include the number of times a
particular browser has been shown a particular ad, or it may include generic information indicating
inferences that have been made about users’ interests. We may also collect non-PII information on
users' activities within the websites of our customers.
We allow third parties to collect and share demographic, intent and interest related data for use in
online advertising, it being made completely clear that any such data is provided only in anonymous,
non-PII form.
HOW DO WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT?

                                                   2
The non-PII that we collect is used in order to provide, operate, manage, maintain, and enhance the
Platform. The non-PII is also used for the purpose of targeting ads and measuring the effectiveness
of ads on behalf of our customers and to identify the audience most likely to respond to an
advertisement. We may also use non-PII data such as demographic, intent and interest related data
we receive from third parties for the purpose of bettering our Platform and Service.
WHAT INFORMATION DO WE SHARE WITH THIRD PARTIES?
Get-more.me may, in order to operate and enhance the Platform or the Service, provide non-PII data
collected on the Platform to customers, partners, and service providers who may use such non-PII for
their commercial purposes. In addition, we may disclose such information in the event we reasonably
believe that we are legally required to do so or in order to take action regarding suspected or actual
prohibited activities. Get-more.me may also share aggregated data derived from the Platform,
including, for example, statistics about Platform activity. Finally, we may transfer non-PII data to a
successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, sale of assets, bankruptcy, or
other corporate change.
Please be advised that we cannot control, monitor or be in any way responsible for any PII that a user
provides to third party websites when clicking on an ad placed through our Platform.
COOKIES AND TRACKING PIXELS
Get-more.me uses cookies and web beacons in connection with our Platform and Service. Cookies
help Get-more.me better understand the effectiveness of our customers' ads (for example, by tracking
the way in which a user may respond to, select and interact with an ad or any content provided therein,
or the location and context in which a user views an ad). Get-more.me's cookies also help control the
number of times a user views a certain ad. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. A
user can instruct his or her browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or prompt the
user before accepting a cookie from the websites the user visits. If the user does not accept cookies,
however, he or she may not be able to enjoy the full functionality of many of the websites he or she
visits.
Get-more.me also uses web beacons, in combination with cookies, to analyze usage patterns. The use
of a web beacon allows us to record that someone has visited a particular webpage, along with
additional Non-PII that the website may choose to include with the beacon.
DATA STORAGE AND SECURITY
All of the user data collected by Get-more.me is stored in such a manner that cannot be tracked back
to specific individuals and information about a specific user cannot be retrieved; we maintain
reasonable physical, electronic, and administrative safeguards to protect all our data from accidental,
unauthorized or unlawful access, use, modification, disclosure, loss, or destruction. However, no
security measures, as thorough as may be, are 100% perfect and there can be no absolute assurance
of security and therefore, we cannot and do not offer an absolute guarantee or warrant the security of
the information we possess.

                                                     3
POLICY TOWARDS CHILDREN
We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13.
If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information
without their consent, he or she should contact us at contact@Get-more.me. If we become aware that
a child under the age of 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information
from our files.
CHANGES AND CONSENT TO PRIVACY POLICY
We reserve the right to change the provisions of this Policy from time to time and it is therefore
recommended to check it regularly. Any updates to our Policy are posted here.
CONTACTING US
For any questions in regards to this Policy or Get-more.me 's privacy practices, please contact our
representatives at the following email and they will be more than happy to clarify and assist you in
any way possible: contact@Get-more.me.
GOVERNING LAW
This Policy shall be exclusively governed by and construed in all respects under the laws of the State
of New York, without giving effect to any choice-of-law or conflict-of-law provisions. Any and all
legal claims, suits or actions that arise in connection with this Policy or with breach of this Policy
shall be submitted to the personal jurisdiction of the courts located in the courts of New York County,
New York.
